# Younis T. Hanafi

High School Senior

DOB: 5<sup>th</sup> April 2004.

Last update in **6<sup>th</sup> Feb. 2022**.

Tags: #STEM\_Luxor'22 #GU\_CCP '21 #Logistics #Entrepreneurship\_researche r #Marketing\_researcher #Robotics #Content\_writer

# **Work Experience**

## The Sparks Foundation

Jan 2022 - Current

#### **STP Academy**

Feb - June 2021

#### **STEMs Guide**

Jan 2020 - Current

## TEDxYouth@QenaSTEM

Mar 2021 - Sep 2021

## TEDxYouth@LuxorSTEM

Apr 2021 - Nov 2021

# **NASA Space Apps Sharkya**

Apr 2021 - Oct 2021

# **Professional Summary**

Expertise in multiple programming languages such as C++, Python, PHP, JS, C#. Expertise in different frameworks like Laravel, React.js. I did numerous projects highlighted in IoT, embedded systems (Arduino), and web development projects. Enthusiastic entrepreneur, marketing researcher, and social media manager. Helped dozens of companies to stand out in the crowd to grow up their businesses on social media. Raised post engagements by 310%, people reached by 1100%, and page like by 500% After doing local/international campaigns. Scientific researcher with numerous DOIs on research gate. Currently a rising senior at Luxor STEM school, an Egyptian STEM school on a merit-based scholarship. In Addition, Georgetown University's college credits program is on a merit-based scholarship.

# IoT and Computer Vision Intern.

- Building Image processing application while going through the ML career essentials.
- Getting familiar with TensorFlow and other Python Al's libraries.

#### Front-end web developer.

Made a full e-learning website, which helps students around the globe in learning and applying what they learned for the international curriculum of Grade 12.

## Founder, CEO & Marketing director

Founded the corporation, made numerous social media campaigns, managed the team, and provided plans for the seasonal experience.

# CEO & Social Media Marketing Manager

- Managed all social media platforms of TEDxYouth@QenaSTEM.
- Trained committee members

# **Information Technology Coordinator**

Coordinating and managing the team members towards a powerful digital standout.

#### **Head Of Information Technology Department**

- Managing and distributing IT members in the event.
- Controlling entrance and exit traffic throughout online platforms in the pandemic.

# **Education**

# Luxor stem school

Sep 2019 - Current

## **Georgetown University**

Jul 2021 - Aug 2021

## High School Diploma, Grade 12

- Founder of LCCC (Luxor Computer Coding Club).
- Member @the Math Club.

## College Credit Courses, Computer Science. Grade: -A

- COSC-010 Python Track
- Summer HOYA for High school students.

# Skills









# Volunteering

#### **IEEE Arabic**

Oct 2020 - Current

## **Google Maps**

Oct 2020 - Current

#### **STEMs Guide**

Jan 2020 - Current

# **Projects**

#### **Black-wheels**

2<sup>nd</sup> Oct - 4<sup>th</sup> Oct 2021

#### **Educational Website**

May 2021 - June 2021

Acidity Preventer Nov 2020 - Feb 2021

# [Project] [Research]

Burns Detector Jan 2020 - Nov 202

# Game it

Oct 2020 - Oct 2020

# Solar Energy: applications and uses. May, 2020 - Jun, 2020

# Languages

#### **Social Media Ambassador**

- Independent & Dependent topics.
- · Trends and blogging

#### **Local Guide**

- Guided +85,500 people to find their destinations.
- Helped +2,000 choosing shops and restaurants.
- +270 Contributions, +160 Answers, +40 facts checked.
- Added +30 photos, +15 reviews, +10 edits, 4 places.

## Founder, CEO & Marketing director

- Helped +4,700 Students in preparatory getting prepared for STEM Schools Admissions tests.
- Provide materials in different subjects and guided students in one-to-one conversations.

# **Embedded Systems developer**

 System for cars to recognize bumps in their way, then it slows down the speed to prevent accidents.

# **Front End developer**

- An educational website that helps the student in learning online during the pandemics.

# **Embedded Systems developer, Scientific Researcher & Writer**

- An Arduino system prevents soil acidity.
- Scientific research for the causes and our proposed solutions.

# Al Developer

- Al Application that detects burns' degree on skins and shows the suitable treatment for patients.

## Unity & C# Developer.

- A game that follows the gamification concept to help encourage children to learn.

#### Scientific Researcher & Writer.

- Scientific research in solar energy, sources, applications, and usages.

| Arabic                          | English                |
|---------------------------------|------------------------|
| Native Or bilingual proficiency | Professional working   |
| French                          | Deutsch                |
| Elementary proficiency          | Elementary proficiency |